class DummyDb {
  static const question = [
    {
      "question": "What is Flutter?",
      "options": [
        "A web development framework",
        "A mobile development framework",
        "A backend framework",
        "A desktop application framework"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which language is used to develop Flutter applications?",
      "options": ["JavaScript", "Dart", "Python", "Swift"],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which widget is used for layout in Flutter?",
      "options": ["Text", "Container", "Column", "Button"],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the default state management approach in Flutter?",
      "options": ["Redux", "Provider", "SetState", "Bloc"],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which command is used to create a new Flutter project?",
      "options": [
        "flutter create projectname",
        "flutter init projectname",
        "flutter start projectname",
        "flutter new projectname"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What is the purpose of the pubspec.yaml file in a Flutter project?",
      "options": [
        "To define the project structure",
        "To manage dependencies and assets",
        "To configure the build process",
        "To write unit tests"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Which widget allows you to build a scrollable list in Flutter?",
      "options": ["GridView", "Column", "ListView", "Stack"],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a StatelessWidget in Flutter?",
      "options": [
        "A widget that does not maintain any state",
        "A widget that maintains state across its lifetime",
        "A widget that is part of the Flutter framework",
        "A widget that handles gestures"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Which method is used to start the execution of a Flutter application?",
      "options": ["main()", "runApp()", "build()", "initState()"],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you add a package dependency in a Flutter project?",
      "options": [
        "Add it to the pubspec.yaml file under dependencies",
        "Run flutter add <package>",
        "Add it to the main.dart file",
        "Run pub add <package>"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    }
  ];
}
